匈牙利  布达佩斯
还没当够士兵啊
Still playing soldiers, huh?
没听说吗  战争早结束了
Haven't you heard? The war's over.
你不还是来了吗
You're here, aren't you?
我们正在筹划大动作
We're planning something big.
最好给我保守秘密是吧
Better keep that to yourself then, huh?
典型的德里人
Derry man obviously.
土生土长的呢
Born and bred.
尘归尘
Earth to earth,
英国  坦布里奇韦尔斯区
土归土
ashes to ashes, dust to dust.
我们在此让瑞秋·道尔顿入土为安
We therefore commit the body of Rachel Dalton to the ground
衷心祈祷
in the sure and certain hope
她能得永生
of resurrection to eternal life.
目标上了电车
Targets are boarding the tram.
包裹即将送达
Package is being delivered.
你有东西要给我们吗
You have something for us?
这个
Here.
我的匈牙利客户
My Hungarian clients
将于明晚提货
will be collecting their shipment tomorrow night.
你还真是全身心投入工作啊  特工小姐
You sure put your heart and soul into your work, special agent.
老话说得好  "不做则已  做即彻底"
Don't they say, "If you're gonna do something, do it right"?
-没错  是有这话  -没错吧
- Yes, I think... I think they do say that. - OK.
里面有一个视频
This contains a video file.
你们已经安排了线人
You have got the connections.
确保送到他们手上
See they get it.
这些家伙喜欢在电视上抛头露面
These guys like to see their faces on the telly all right.
我有新生活了  我不能...
I have a new life out here. I can't--
你不做不行
You will do this.
你听见他说的话了
You heard the man.
什么时间
When?
你会知道的
You will know.
别回头
Don't turn round.
别说话
Keep your mouth shut.
好久不见  肖恩
Long time no see, Sean.
你他妈到底是从哪冒出来的
Where the fuck did you come from?
来自过去
Out of the past.
你有些生疏了  肖恩
You're getting rusty, Sean.
我现在是守法公民
I'm legit now.
生意人
I'm a businessman.
当然
Of course you are.
以前是往贝尔法斯特走私军火
All those years running guns into Belfast,
贝尔法斯特  北爱尔兰首府
现在又来布达佩斯赚外快
and now you supply from Budapest.
说说看  你最近准备送谁圣诞礼物
So tell me, who's on your Christmas card list these days--
朱海瑞吗
Al-Zuhari?
没听过这人
Never heard of him.
-那马芮·麦坎娜呢  -谁
- What about Mairead McKenna? - Who?
我们知道她去了布达佩斯后
Soon as we knew she was headed for Budapest,
便立即查了你的通话记录  肖恩
we pulled your phone records, Sean.
她两天前从贝鲁特打电话给你
She rang you from Beirut two days ago.
你这是在玩火  肖恩
You're playing a very dangerous game, Sean.
欧瑞沃登
O'Riordan!
滚开
Hey! Fuck off!
后退  不然我开枪了
Get back, or I'll shoot.
包围他
Contain!
我警告你们
I'm warning youse!
快他妈滚开
Get the fuck away from me!
上  上
Go, go, go.
记住  要抓活的
Remember, we need him alive!
快点
Hurry!
爱尔兰人  喂
Irish, oi, oi!
听着  听着
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Look, look, look.
-我们想跟你谈谈  -离我远点
- We just want to talk. - Back off.
-不  我们只想跟你谈谈  -滚开
- No. Hey. We just want to talk. - Back off!
放开我  你...
Get off me, you--
能借你的假发一用吗
Can I have your wig?
戴这儿
Right here!
-瞧这哥们儿  -快把那玩意拿走
- Oi, fella! - Get that thing off me!
-我爱你  哥们  -他要结婚啦
-I love you, buddy. - He's getting married.
-来不来  -没问题  走你
- Shall we? - Yeah. Go.
不  不
No! No!
好玩不
There you go.
我招  我招
OK, OK!
你想戴着绿假发死吗
You want to die in a green wig?
招了吧  肖恩
Come on, Sean.
-招了吧  -快把我弄上去
- Come on. - I said just please get me up.
那好吧
Yeah, all right.
说吧  肖恩  说说麦坎娜的事
Come on, Sean. Talk to me about McKenna.
我只和她的手下打过交道
I only dealt with her crew.
他们想要什么
And what did they want?
跟以前一样  武器和炸药
Same thing they always want-- weapons and explosives.
还有呢
Mm-hmm. More, more.
没了
That's your lot.
弄回去
Back over.
不  不
No, no!
-来了  喜欢吗哥们  -好吧
- There you go, buddy. Like that? - All right.
我让他们去一个
I pointed them at arms shipment
位于佩斯的转运站
coming into the switching yard
那里明晚会运来一批武器
tomorrow night in Pest.
麦坎娜打算在那里设埋伏
McKenna's going to ambush it.
麦坎娜为什么杀了瑞秋·道尔顿
Why the fuck did McKenna kill Rachel Dalton?
瑞秋·道尔顿是什么人
Who the fuck is Rachel Dalton?
我们该去哪找麦坎娜
Where can we find McKenna?
她明晚会在那的
She'll be there tomorrow night.
好吧  起来吧
Yeah. Up you go.
你没撒谎吧  肖恩
Now you wouldn't lie to me, would you, Sean?
我都是有孙子的人了
I have grandchildren.
我向上帝发誓  我说的绝对是实话
I swear to God it's the honest truth.
-搜身  -是  长官
- Search him. - Yes, sir.
你他妈把手拿开
Get your fucking hands off of me!
冷静  冷静点
Calm down, calm down.
一起散散步
Let's go for a walk.
来散散步  大块头
Let's take a walk, big fella.
绿巨人啊你
Kelly green giant, huh?
你好啊  哥们
How you doing, folks?
头儿
Boss!
别干傻事  肖恩
Ah, don't be silly, Sean.
蠢货
Stupid fucker.
我先走了
I'm out.
该死
Shit.
布达佩斯  英国使馆
钻石那件事  你不会突然就怂了吧
You're not gonna chicken out on me with those diamonds, are you?
不知道
I don't know.
拜托阿迈  那些钻石是坏人的
Come on, Mikey. They're bad guy diamonds.
你要是上交了  上级会把它们
You hand them in, and our guys are gonna give them back
还给黎巴嫩政府的
to the Lebanese authorities,
最后可能还得落到真主党手中
who are probably gonna give them back to Hezbollah.
他们只会买更多军火  杀掉更多我们的人
They're just gonna buy more guns and kill more of our guys.
也就是说  我们打破了恶性循环
Well... So... we're just breaking the cycle.
没错  我们其实是帮了大伙一把是吧
Yeah. We're just doing everyone a favor, aren't we?
正是
Exactly.
这世界够乱了
It's a messed up world.
谁说不是呢
It certainly is.
就是说  说到这个
Yeah. Speaking of which,
我看见你和马丁内斯亲嘴了
saw you and Martinez out there having a little smoochy smooch.
哥们  只是掩护身份而已
Just maintaining my cover, mate.
-真的吗  -没错
- Really? - Yeah.
吻的可带劲了
Doing a very good job.
是嘛  多谢夸奖
Oh. Well, cheers.
很高兴看到你又做了回男人
Glad to see you're finally getting some action.
请出示证件  先生们
Identification, gentlemen.
等一下  我们是来找...
Uh, hang on. We're with--
是斯科特和斯顿布奇中士吗
Sergeants Scott and Stonebridge?
找她的
Her.
请止步
Stop, please.
你是哪位
And you are?
反正你高攀不起就对了
Out of your league.
纳塔丽·费希尔
Natalie Fisher.
我们在使馆宴会厅搭建了你们的设备
We've set up your facility in the embassy ballroom.
-跟我来  -多谢
- Follow me. - Thank you.
我想这两位是你的人吧
Two of yours, I believe.
情况如何
How was it?
凄凉  爱尔兰共和军的葬礼比我们体面多了
Bleak. The IRA give their dead a better sendoff.
是啊  我都应该出席她的葬礼才对
Yeah. I still think we should have been there.
可惜去哪执行任务不是我们能左右的
Sadly we don't get to choose where we're sent.
她有一个儿子
She had a son.
不是吧
No shit.
你知道吗
Did you know?
我也是后来才知道
No. Not until after.
我们会尽量安顿好这个孩子
We'll do what we can for the boy.
因为军队不肯管是吗
What, because the army won't, right?
迈克尔  由于战士牺牲
They're not the first family
而造成的残破家庭太多了
to pay the price for what we do, Michael.
是
Sir.
线上来电
Coming online.
-嘿  小姑娘  -你好
- Hey, kid. - Hi.
最近还好吧
How you doing?
不好  嚼着尼古丁口香糖呢
Uh, not good. Nicotine gum.
那玩意儿没用  试试别的
That shit doesn't work. Try something else.
瑞士怎么样
How's Switzerland?
有点无聊  没有枪战什么的
Uh, it's a bit boring. There's no gun battles.
我很想你们
Aw. I miss you guys.
这位老妈子每晚想你想得以泪洗面
Yeah. Mom here has been crying into her pillow every night.
对  没错
Yeah, it's true.
那你呢
And you?
有点儿吧
I miss you a little.
是想极了
A lot.
差不多了
Ok.
哦  那再见了
Oh. I'll see you later.
-拜拜  -再见
- Bye-bye. - See you.
把门关上
Close the door.
李奥  很高兴你能加入我们
Glad you could join us, Leo.
我们破解了在欧瑞沃登身上找到的这段视频
We've decrypted the media file found on O'Riordan's body.
如今这场在欧洲展开的战役...
The attack you have witnessed in Europe today...
是朱海瑞
Al-Zuhari.
是你们咎由自取的结果
you have brought on your own heads.
在伊玛·阿里·阿拉亚西斯·萨拉姆的
On the anniversary of the martyrdom of Imam Ali,
殉难纪念日上
Alayahis Salam,
你们已经感受到了我们每天经受的痛苦
you have tasted what we must live with every day.
除非你们的政府从所有
Until your governments withdraw from all lands
不欢迎你们的土地上撤军
where you are unwanted,
我们将携手
we and our brothers
世界上所有受压迫国家的兄弟们
from oppressed nations of this earth
将安拉的怒火撒在你们的头上
will rain the fire of Allah on your heads.
去你妈的
Fuck you, too.
卡马里  这段视频会在攻击后进行直播对吧
Kamali, this is for broadcast after an attack, right?
没错  而且我们最多只有48小时
Yeah, and at most, we have 48 hours.
他所说的圣日就是本周三
The holy day he refers to is on Wednesday.
除了携带朱海瑞联合公报的共和军成员
So we have an IRA man with an Al-Zuhari communiqué?
我们还获悉即将遭到伏击的军火物资
and an arms shipment that's about to be ambushed.
李奥  我需要你过来
Leo, I need you here.
有点困难  艾斯特...
It's difficult. Ester--
不管  李奥你一定要来
No. I need you here, Leo.
那我安排一下
I'll make arrangements.
谢谢  非常感谢
Thank you. I appreciate it.
听好了
All right. Listen up.
这不仅是一场恐怖袭击
This isn't just a terrorist attack.
我们目前的处境
What we're looking at here
是过去十年来所有特工的噩梦
has been every operative's worst nightmare for the last decade--
那就是新老敌人携手联合
the old enemy are joining hands with the new.
为了不让麦坎娜得到那些武器
So we prevent McKenna from getting hold of those weapons,
我们就得搞清朱海瑞耍的花招
we find out what Al-Zuhari's playing at,
并加以阻止
and we stop it.
喂  拿去
Yo. There you go.
嘿  喂
Hey! Oi!
打个盹儿就亏大了
Snooze you lose.
为此我们应该喝一杯
We should drink to that.
就该为这干一杯
That's what we should drink to.
喝好
Enjoy.
真要为这个干杯吗
Is that what we're gonna drink to?
我们应该敬道尔顿
We should drink to Dalton.
她曾是我们的一份子
She was one of us.
天呐  不是吧
God. Heh. Really?
你开玩笑吧
You fucking kidding me?
她都不把你当人看
She treated you like shit,
天知道她有多少次
and God knows how many times
害得我们差点没命
she nearly got all of us fucking killed.
达米恩  也许等过了这阵子  也许...
Damian, if maybe we could go through our time, maybe--
得了吧  兄弟
Oh, come on, dude.
我们在她手下干了那么久  连她尸体都抬过
We were always there, we all fucking carried her.
好吧  我知道她有个孩子
Yeah. I know she's got a little kid,
我也真心为那个男孩感到惋惜
and I'm really sorry for that little boy.
如果非说她死了令我很难过的话
I'd be a fucking liar
就太对不起良心了
if I said I wasn't glad she wasn't here.
抱歉  下一轮算我的
Sorry. Next round's on me.
不好意思  我不会匈牙利语
I'm sorry. I don't speak Hungarian.
从没见过你
Haven't see you before.
初到这个城市
First time in the city.
你在布达佩斯工作吗
Do you work here in Budapest?
在大使馆
Embassy.
外交官呀
A diplomat.
哇  那工作一定体面极了
Wow! That must be glamorous.
那具体做些什么呢
What exactly is it you do?
无穷尽的接待工作
Endless receptions, being hit on by
被出门在外  兴奋过头的生意人搭讪
overexcited businessmen away from home.
真是少女的梦想啊
Every girl's dream, huh?
你那么说道尔顿没错
You were right about Dalton.
谢了
Thanks.
0个匹配
前女友吗
Old girlfriend?
没错
Yeah.
她没准儿结了婚  改了姓
She could have got married, changed her name.
是啊
Yeah.
这样  这事交给我来办
Look. Leave it with me.
都是为了国家  对吧
Things we do for our country, eh?
不计代价
Whatever it takes.
你真是个小可爱  不是吗
You're a wee darling, aren't you?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
布达佩斯  转运站
我们知道朱海瑞的进攻迫在眉睫
We know Al-Zuhari is planning an imminent attack.
欧瑞沃登告诉我们的这批军火
The arms shipment O'Riordan told us about
将在今晚用火车运抵
arrives by train tonight.
如果我们无法阻止麦坎娜的人
If we don't stop McKenna's crew
拿到那些武器
getting their hands on those weapons,
我们就会失去有关朱海瑞袭击的唯一线索
we lose the only lead we have of the Al-Zuhari attack,
而哥伦比亚和贝鲁特的行动也会成为徒劳
so Colombia, Beirut will all have been for nothing.
各位  我要你们赶在火车到达
Guys, I need you on that train before
布达佩斯前潜入列车
it reaches Budapest.
马丁内斯
Martinez,
你去转运站等他们  好吗
you'll be waiting for them at the switching yard, OK?
麦坎娜要抓活的
Bring me back McKenna alive.
她来了
There she is.
好吧
All right.
布奇与桑德斯为电影《虎豹小霸王》中的角色
我是布奇  你是桑德斯
I'm Butch, and you're Sundance.
桑德斯跑得快
Sundance was faster.
但布奇比较帅
Yeah, but Butch was better looking.
但桑德斯有女朋友
Yeah, but Sundance got the girl.
说得好  那你可不是桑德斯
Good point. You can't be Sundance.
好了  最后一节车厢?
All right. Get the last car?
没错  就是它了  就是它了
Yeah. That's us, that's us.
行了  里面没人
Yeah. No one in here.
B2  你们就位了吗
Bravo Two, are you in position?
两位流浪汉已坐上火车出发了
There's two hobos on board and on the way.
收到  卫星马上连线
Roger. Sat coming online now.
喂  你觉得布奇和桑德斯最后死了吗
Oi. Do you think Butch and Sundance die at the end?
不会的伙计  他们没死
No, dude. They lived.
两个人对抗整个玻利维亚军队
Just two men against the entire Bolivian army.
话说我们也干过这事  对吧
Been there and done that, huh?
所以说  他们肯定没死
Well, they definitely lived.
一直没人发现他们的尸体
They never found the bodies.
所以那两个人带着赃物一起消失了
So those two just disappeared with all that loot.
没错
Yeah.
知道吗  有时候
You know, sometimes,
你得知道什么时候应该及时抽身
you got to know when you got to go.
好吧  咱们给钻石估估价
All right. Let's get the diamonds valued
但只是出于好奇  仅此而已
but just out of curiosity, that's all.
要是我们啥时候栽在敌人手上
God knows, if we fall on our faces,
可没人会来接我们回去
nobody's gonna pick us up.
这是一定的
That much is clear.
就位  完毕
In position. Over.
收到  有什么情况吗  完毕
Roger. Any activity? Over.
没有  完毕
Negative. Out.
匈牙利人来拿货了
Hungarians are making the pickup.
卸完货就离开这
加油  快点
阿迈  我要上了
Mikey, I'm moving.
祝你好运
Good luck.
快点卸货
把那箱子给我
是我们要的货
他们拿到了些重武器
They've got some heavy-duty shit here.
没有发现爱尔兰共和军的行踪
There's no sign of the Irish guys.
等等  12点方向有狙击手
Hold up. I got a sniper at my 12
就在那座桥上
up on that bridge.
真是进行伏击的好位置
Good position if they ambush, huh?
敌军已确认
X-ray confirmed.
哦  该死
Oh, fuck.
把你的手举起来
Put your fucking hands up.
跪下
Down on your knees.
王八蛋
Motherfucker.
爱尔兰战士来了
Here's the fightin' Irish.
求求你
不要杀我
该死  他们杀光了匈牙利人
Shit. They've finished off the Hungarians.
快点  警察很快就会来的
Come on! Cops will be all over this place soon!
首要目标射击视野清晰
I got a clear shot at our primary target.
把它装到货车上去
Put it in the lorry.
该死的廉姆他人呢
Where the fuck's Liam?
她有两个手下是中东人
Two of her crew are Middle Eastern.
在这等着  把枪运走  动作快
Wait here. Move those guns now! Quickly!
目标开始移动
Target's on the move.
如果可以的话  拿下她
If you can, take her
要活的  B2
alive, Bravo Two.
明白
Copy that.
他妈的快搬  你他妈在度假吗
Move the fuck out! You on fucking holiday?
-快点行动  -来搬这个
- Come on. Let's go! - Let's shift this.
搬上去
Move it!
快点  我们走
Come on. Let's go.
该死的  廉姆
Shit! Liam!
操  谁开的火
Fuck. Who the fuck's firing?
趴下
Get down!
是冲我们来的  我们非战不可
They're on us. We have a fight.
不
No!
目标已擒获
Target acquired.
去把卡车开来带我们离开
Get the truck and take us out!
快  离开这儿
Move it! Get out of here!
去开车  去开车
Get the truck, get the truck!
长官  他们要走了
Boss, they're on the move.
武器在卡车上
The weapons are on the truck.
别让他们带着武器离开
Do not let them get away with those weapons.
开什么玩笑
Are you fucking kidding me?
上  阿迈
Go, Mikey!
射击
Take the shot.
拜托
Come on.
射击
Take the shot.
操
Fuck.
妈的
Shit.
该死
布达佩斯  英国使馆
有关于军火车的消息吗
Any news on the arms truck?
还没有  当地警方已高度警戒
Nothing yet. Local police have been alerted,
国家通讯中心...
an GCHQ...
我们都有失手的时候  阿迈
We all miss sometimes, Mikey.
即使像我们这样厉害的人也不例外
Happens to the best of us.
是吗  但我瞄准了
Yeah? Well, I had it.
别对自己太过苛刻  伙计
Don't be too hard on yourself, dude.
当时那么黑  目标还在移动
It was dark, it was a moving target.
妈的  我说我瞄准了  斯科特
I said I fucking had it, Scott.
你只是觉得需要做个健康检查是吗
So you just felt like getting a checkup, huh?
是的  没错
Yes. Yeah.
你肯定是有史以来第一个
You must be the first man in history
主动上门拜访医生的人
to voluntarily visit a doctor.
只是很久没做检查了而已
It's just been a while, that's all.
常规血样检查
Routine blood sample.
结果会在几天内送交你们的指挥官
Results will be passed to your CO in a couple of days.
有什么事困扰着你吗  中士
Something bothering you, sergeant?
不  不  什么都没有
No. No, nothing.
焦虑  情绪不稳定
Anxiety, mood swings?
不  我觉得没有
No, no, not that I can think of.
我曾在地方自卫队服役  去过两次伊拉克
I used to be Territorial Army, two tours, Iraq.
我的号码  可以随时联系我
My number. Any time you want to talk.
来吧
Go on.
过去  爱尔兰共和军常常
Back in the day, the IRA used to
把精神集中在无形的火焰上
concentrate their minds on an invisible flame
以此抵抗审讯
to resist interrogation.
你是指折磨吧
You mean torture.
水刑可不是美国佬发明的
It wasn't the yanks invented waterboarding.
你们在四十年前就对我们用过了
You were using it on us 40 years ago.
"我们"?  有意思
"Us"? That's interesting.
你不是爱尔兰共和军的人  马芮
You're not IRA, Mairead.
否则你早该知道战争已经结束了
If you were, you would know the war's over.
爱尔兰共和军  他们追求的东西
The IRA-- what they settled for
本该在我出生前十年就已经得到了满足
we could have had 10 years before I was born.
那么你是什么人
So what are you?
哦  别告诉我
Oh, don't tell me.
你是真爱尔兰共和军
you're the Real IRA, hmm?
你真觉得人们相信那个吗
Do you really think people believe that?
你在那服过役吗
You serve there?
曾上过6次战场
6 tours.
阿尔马[北爱尔兰]  八十年代中期吗
Armagh, mid-eighties?
那你应该见过我哥哥
You'd have met my brother then.
也可能没见过
Or maybe not.
否则活不到今日
You're still alive.
你在贝鲁特干什么
What were you doing in Beirut, hmm?
你跟志同道合的圣战分子合作吗
You teaming up with some like-minded jihadists?
你打算将伊斯兰教法带去你们那六县
You gonna bring Sharia law to the 6 counties
将北爱尔兰变成穆斯林国家吗
and turn the North into some Muslim caliphate?
穆斯林也比英国人好
Better the Muslims than the British.
你不会真的这么想吧
Oh, you don't really believe that.
你手下在哪  卡车在哪
Where are your boys? Where's the truck?
什么时候发动袭击
When is this attack going to take place?
是他妈的臭英军抓走了马芮
It was the fucking Brits took Mairead.
闻都能闻出来
Could smell the bastards.
他快不行了
He's dying.
那快给他找个神父呀
So he needs a fucking priest!
袭击必须按计划进行
The attack must go ahead.
我们去救她出来
We'll get her out.
使馆里有人
Got connections in the consulate.
神父
Father...
他需要临终祈祷  神父
He needs the last rites, father.
现在没时间搞这事
There's no time for this.
你他妈的放尊重点
Show some fucking respect!
我们这下有麻烦了
We have a problem here.
你的烂摊子得自己清理干净
You have to clean up your mess.
马芮  跟我说说
So tell me, Mairead,
你为什么要杀道尔顿少校
why did you kill Major Dalton?
贝鲁特那女的吗
The girl in Beirut?
只怪那婊子出现在错误时间错误的地点
Bitch was in the wrong place at the wrong time,
战争的牺牲品而已
casualty of war.
那索菲亚·阿布德  朱海瑞的妻子呢
And Sofia Abboud, Al-Zuhari's wife?
她可能会暴露我们的行动
She could have compromised our operation.
你跟这些人合作能得到什么好处啊
What can you possibly get out of working with these people?
我现在都可以想象
I get to see the look on your face
当你意识到几千年来被你们践踏的人民
when you realize every fucker you ever trod on
全部联合起来
for the past thousand years
找你们算账时  你脸上那操蛋的表情
has clubbed together and is coming back to get you.
别废话了  告诉我目标是什么
Come on. Tell me about the target.
我可以保守秘密
I can keep a secret.
问问你哥就知道
Ask your brother.
-我哥已死了  -我知道
- My brother's dead. - I know.
他在福尔斯路的岩石酒吧外
He was picked up outside the Rock Bar on the Falls Road
被政府暗杀小组带走的
by a loyalist hit squad.
你调查得很详细啊
You've done your research.
想要什么  金星奖章吗
What you want, a gold star?
我当时在场
I was there.
我认识你哥哥  马芮
Ooh. I knew your brother, Mairead.
那正是我的工作
It was my job to.
但你私底下也认识他
But you knew him personally,
竟然能遇见他
you ran across him.
我派他去的
I ran him.
什么
What?
你听到了
You heard.
你哥哥是间谍
Your brother was a tout.
你这卑鄙的英国小人
You dirty Brit bastard.
我哥比你好上十倍
My brother was worth 10 of you.
他把你们伟大的特种空勤团
He had you lot running scared,
吓得屁滚尿流
the great SAS.
你变成这样  都是因为你哥哥
Everything you are you are because of your brother,
而你所知道关于他的一切
and everything you know about him
都是谎言
was a lie.
你才是说谎的那个
You're the liar.
长官
Sir.
好好想想吧
Think about that.
当地警方接到
Local police just got a call
来自五号区一所教堂的报案
from a church in District 5.
教堂里一位神父
One of their priests has been kidnapped
在帮一名身中枪伤的男子
as he gave the last rites
做临终祈祷时被绑架了
to a man dying of gunshot wound.
男子好像是被一个阿拉伯人
Seems he was brought in by an Arab
和一个爱尔兰人带来的
and an Irishman.
好  去调查下
OK. Check it out.
好的  收到
Yeah. Roger that.
但把行动权叫给匈牙利警方
But give the Hungarians operational control.
明白
Will do.
爱尔兰领事馆一直在找大使
The Irish Consulate has been on to the ambassador.
帮我找娜塔莉进来
Get Natalie in here, will you?
她今天没来上班  长官
She didn't come in today, sir.
中士
Hey, sergeant.
怎么了
Yeah?
什么时候一起吃个晚餐吧
Want to grab dinner sometime?
不用很正式
You know, nothing too serious,
只要有美食美酒  还有
just some good food, fine wine, and...
超带劲的滚床单就行
hot butt-naked sex.
你真觉得现在适合聊这个话题吗
You really think now's the time to talk about that?
考虑到我们可能一分钟后就归天了
Well, given that we could be dead in 60 seconds,
不借此刻 更待何时
I'd say there's no time like the present.
快  快上
Go, go, go! Go, go, go! Go!
你没事吧
You all right?
阿迈
Mikey?!
我们没事  你呢
Yeah. We're all right. You OK?
是什么叼东西
What the fuck was that?
弗兰西害得我们老是跑银行
Oh, yeah. Francie had us running to the bank.
我们每年得支付他五万英镑
50 grand a year we pumped into his account
还没算其他花销
plus expenses.
不过
Still...
钱的确花对地方了
it was money well spent.
没附加条件吧
No strings attached?
晚饭各付各的就行
As long as we can go Dutch.
行  就这么办
Yeah. Yeah, we can.
靠
Shit.
卑鄙的爱尔兰混蛋
Sneaky Irish bastards.
对
Yeah.
-卑鄙小人 -没错  哥们
- Pricks. - Yeah, dude.
我们该金盆洗手了  阿迈
We got to get out of this game, Mikey.
即便不是爱尔兰共和军
You know, if it's not the IRA,
我们也可能被其他混账干掉
it's just gonna be some other fucker that gets us.
哥们  刚才真差点没命啊
Dude, that was way too close,
就他妈差一点点
way too fucking close.
是啊
Yeah.
操
Fuck!
的确是
Yes, it was.
全都是扯谈
This is bullshit.
会电脑的小鬼十分钟内就能伪造出来
Kid with a Mac could fake this shit up in 10 minutes.
是吗
Yeah?
好吧
Ok.
看看这个
Try this.
你好  弗兰西
Hey, Francie.
来自英国政府的一点小礼物
Just a little present from Her Majesty's Government.
两名士兵因你才得以继续活下去  弗兰西
Two soldiers still walking the streets because of you, Francie.
多谢了  你还有其他事跟我汇报吗
Thank you. Now you have something for me?
会有一次袭击
An attack.
就今晚  库申多尔的警察局
Tonight. Police station in Cushendall.
细节都在那里面
Details are in there.
弗兰西  你是个好人
Francie, good man.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
你手下那帮人愿意听从你指挥
The crew you're running only defer to you
全因为你哥哥
because of who your brother was,
他们眼中的他
who they think he was.
爱尔兰共和军出于同样原因才没有消灭你
Same reason the actual IRA hasn't wiped you out.
因为你是弗兰西·麦坎娜的妹妹
You're Francie McKenna's wee sister.
他们不会动你一根汗毛
You're untouchable.
我把这段视频放到共和党的新闻网站上
Let's see how well that holds when I post this
看看结果会怎么样  如何
on a Republican news web site, shall we?
亵童者都要比告密者高尚吧  马芮
Better a child molester than an informer, eh, Mairead?
袭击是什么时候
The attack, when is it,
在哪里
where is it?
最后一次机会  马芮
Last chance, Mairead.
洛克上校
Colonel Locke?
借一步说话
A word.
你就是菲利普·洛克吗
Would that be the Philip Locke?
拜托
Please.
大使马上就要朝你头上扣屎盆子了
The ambassador's about to bring a shitstorm down on your head.
爱尔兰领事馆知道我们抓住了麦坎娜
The Irish Consulate know that we're holding McKenna.
他们威胁说要把这事捅到首相那儿去
They're threatening to take it to Number 10,
并指责我们把大使馆当作秘密基地
claim we're using the embassy as a black site
进行非法引渡
for illegal renditions.
她说你们一定要把麦坎娜送去伦敦
She's assured them you're going to take McKenna to London
现在就去
now.
你是认真的吗
Are you serious?
一场袭击即将发生
An attack is about to take place,
她是我们唯一的线索
and she is the only lead we have.
她必须走  菲利普
She has to go, Philip,
而且必须走官方程序
and it has to be official.
这太他妈扯蛋了
This is bullshit.
袭击迫在眉睫
An imminent attack,
而我们却无法审讯袭击的策划者
and we can't question the terrorist who's planning it
就因为我们不在自己国家
because we're in the wrong fucking country?
如果你们中情局没有
Perhaps if your CIA hadn't set up
搞出那套全球刑讯特许权网络
its own global network of torture franchises,
我们就不会陷入如此境地了
we wouldn't be in this situation now.
把她送上飞机之后
As soon as the wheels go up on that plane,
你们就立刻回这儿来
I need you lot back here.
-明白  -遵命
- Boss. - Sir.
你的儿子怎么样  菲利普
How's your son, Philip?
现在几岁了  20还是25
Be what now, 20, 25?
胆敢再提我的儿子
You mention my son again,
我就立刻杀了你
and I will kill you where you stand.
明白吗
Have you got that?
长官
Boss.
押她上车
Get her in the car.
你跟她一辆车
You ride with her.
怎么  就因为我说的那句话?
What, was it something I said?
上车
Get in.
这么兴师动众
All this for me.
我把你们吓破胆了吧
Scare you boys, do I?
说到贝鲁特  别总是想到下雨
Don't normally think of rain when you think of Beirut,
但我猜你们现在就想到了那场雨
but I bet you do now.
她求我饶命
She begged me for her life.
她叫什么  道尔顿
What was her name-- Dalton?
和你们一样
Like all of you boys,
她擅长打人  却经不起挨打
she was better dishing it out than taking it.
好了  你们知道规矩
OK. You know the score.
遵守外交礼节
Diplomatic protocols apply.
枪都锁在箱子里
Guns in lock boxes,
这里过去有9码远
the whole 9 yards.
对  我们就像待宰羔羊
Yeah. We'll be sitting ducks.
我要上厕所
I need to use the bathroom.
亲爱的  你想得美
Hmm. Nice try, sweetheart.
你可以上了飞机再去
You can do it on the plane.
我要押送一个犯人回英国
I'm taking a prisoner back to the U.K.
这些人会和我一起上飞机
These people are seeing me on the plane.
所有的文书都在这儿
The paperwork's all here,
我们的飞机就在那条跑道上
and our jet's on the runway over there.
我要看所有人的护照
I need to see everyone's passports.
谢了  老爸
Thanks, Dad.
你们都没有入境记录
There's no record of your arrival.
我们乘外交航班从贝鲁特来这儿的
It was a diplomatic flight from Beirut.
她有护照吗
She has a passport?
-老天爷  -请等一下
- Oh, for God's sake. - One minute, please.
别开玩笑好吗
Fucking joking, right?
这女人是个被通缉的恐怖分子
Look. This woman is a wanted terrorist
她需要被引渡到英国去
who's being extradited to the U.K.
这已经板上钉钉了
It's been cleared.
你看文件就知道了
You need to read that.
恐怕你们得在这等一下  先生们
I'm afraid I'm going to have to ask you to wait here, gentlemen.
让我上飞机  或者让我上厕所
Get me on that plane, or let me use the bathroom.
闭上你的嘴
Shut the fuck up.
每个月总有那么几天
Time of the month.
看在老天的份上  你们也是女人
For God's sake, you're women.
带她去吧
Just take her.
走吧
Let's go.
你们得把这个解开
I'm gonna need these off.
这样我怎么上厕所
How am I supposed to go?
自己想办法
You'll figure it out.
进去吧
It's all yours.
好了  一切都没有问题
OK. Everything seems in order.
花了这么长时间
About fucking time.
走吧
Let's go.
谢谢
Cheers.
请交出你的枪
Your guns, please.
我没带枪
I haven't got one.
骗你们的
Eh, just fucking with you.
放好了  别弄丢
Here. Don't lose it.
从这里走过来  先生
Step this way, sir.
等一下
Hold on.
快一点
Hurry up.
用这个
Right there.
走这边
Step this way.
你扫出他带的金属鸡鸡吗
Ha! You find his metal dildo?
对  谢了  伙计
Yeah. Thanks, mate.
那几个女的怎么还不回来
Where are those fucking girls?
你可以进去了
You can go through.
上  快上
Move, move, move!
起来  大块头
Come here, big guy.
在二楼走廊  迈克
On the balcony, Mikey!
放下枪  快
Drop the gun. Do it.
准备移动
I'm moving!
上  迈克
Go, Mike!
快扔
Now!
谢了
Thank you.
待在那儿  待在那儿  别动
Stay there. Stay right there. Don't move!
该死
Shit.
快开枪  迈克尔
Take the shot, Michael.
迈克  快开枪
Mikey, take that shot!
开枪
Take it.
你个混蛋想得美
Don't even think about it, you fucker.
你是我的
You're mine!
他妈的
Fuck!
该死
Fuck.
马芮  你他妈的搞什么
What the fuck, Mairead? What are you doing?
快走  就现在
Move it! Go! Now.
他妈的
Fuck!
走  伙计  快走
Go, man! Move!
朱莉娅
Julia.
该死
Fuck.
给我个手雷
Give me a fucking grenade!